

ABOUT ME

Working as a frontend developer for over 4 years, using JavaScript/
Typescript to create web UIs. I am excited to experiment with new UI designs and learn new technologies. Building UIs with different technologies is challenging, but it helps me enhance my skills.

CONTACT





Fajrin Mahyuddin

SKILLS

[ExpressJS] PHP] ReactJS CSS] Rest API Laravel Jquery Styled Component | ReactNative Scss / Sass / Less Svelte NextJS Typescript Firebase Javascript InertiaJS (GraphQL) Supabse

NodeJS

HOBBIES

ThreeJS







FAJRIN MAHYUDDIN

Front End Developer



EDUCATION

Diploma III of Electrical Engineering at State Polytechnic of Ujung Pandang, 2012 - 2015

Bachelor Degree of Electrical Engineering at Tadulako University, 2017 - 2019

JOB

EXPERIENCE

Remote - Frontend Developer, Oct 2021 - May 2024 at Zodiac Solution Pte Ltd (Singapore)

- R&D to try AI technology and 3D web view.
- Optimize web applications.
- EDM design using MJML.
- Collaborated with backend/UI-UX/unity team.
- Create, review, and testing project based on requirements.
- Implementing best practice method.
- Maintaining previous projects.
- Implementing 3D web view using ThreeJS

Remote/Hybrid - Frontend Dev, Nov 2019 - Oct 2021 at Pallaka Studio (Makassar - Indonesia)

- Optimize web applications.
- Collaborated with backend dan UI-UX team.
- Planning development process with whole team.
- Create UI based on design.
- Implementing best practice method.
- Maintaining previous projects.
- Container deployment using docker.

Fullstack Developer, Jan 2016 - Aug 2016 at PT Cipta Sejati Revolution (Makassar - Indonesia)

- Craft the application's design before diving into development.
- Maintaining preview applications.
- Create, review, and testing project based on requirements.
- Implementing best practice method.
- Setup and deploy to the server.
- Maintenance server and internet at office.

FIND ME

Official Site - https://fajrin-mahyuddin.github.io

Github - https://github.com/Fajrin-Mahyuddin

Linkedin - https://www.linkedin.com/in/fajrin-mahyuddin

Twitter - @Fajrin_M